Joshua Bergeron

pacluc20@gmail.com, (858) 204-3675

OBJECTIVE

I am a first-year college student and will transfer to a four-year university to pursue a computer science degree in the Fall of 2022. Due to having a significant number of AP test credits and a rigorous course load, I will complete my general education requirements by the end of this academic year (Spring 2022). I am seeking an internship for the Summer of 2022 to gain experience and help prepare me for my future career in software engineering.

SKILLS

- Python and Java
- Problem-Solving and Critical Thinking
- Teamwork and Communication
- Diligent and Hardworking

EDUCATION

Palomar College, San Marcos, CA

Summer 2021 - Spring 2022 (Transfer to UC or CSU Fall 2022)

- General Education will be completed by the end of Spring 2022
- Taking Data Structures and Machine Assembly classes Spring 2022

Mission Hills High School, San Marcos, CA

2017-2021 (Graduated June 2021 - Overall GPA: 4.41)

- Python and Java classes
- AP/Honors classes
- National Honor Society
- Informal peer tutoring
- Varsity Boys Tennis Team (4 years)

EXPERIENCE

Mathnasium of San Marcos - Lead Math Tutor

November 2019 - Present

- Tutor students in math grades K-12 (up through Calculus) with an emphasis on strengthening areas of student struggle
- Multitasking and teamwork tutoring several students at once
- Serve as a role model to the students I tutor

LEGOLAND California Resort - Retail Associate

May 2019 - August 2019 (Summer Job)

- Restocked the store, had good product knowledge, store cleanliness, and processed transactions
- Created personalized experiences for each guest

VOLUNTEERING

Shooting Stars Basketball, San Marcos, CA

Assisted in helping children with special needs play basketball for three (3) years

Community Lutheran Church, Escondido

• Volunteered for three (3) years completing various service events

AWARDS

- AP Scholar with Distinction 2020-2021 (High school)
- "Best Buddies" from Shooting Stars Basketball volunteer work
- Rookie of the Year, Best Doubles Team, and Avocado League Doubles Champion (Tennis)